<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jpsl on bayesian boondoggles</title>
    <link>/authors/jpsl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jpsl on bayesian boondoggles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Jeremiah Lewis</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/authors/jpsl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science In 5 Links</title>
      <link>/post/five-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/five-links/</guid>
      <description> Bayesian Statistics  Statistical Rethinking Towards a Principled Bayesian Workflow brms R Package Stan User&amp;rsquo;s Guide Bayesian Data Analysis Textbook  Open Data  Open Corporates Open Data Handbook openaq: Open Air Quality EU Open Data Portal Copernicus Open Remote Sensing Data  Data Science Team Management  How to Decide which Data Science Projects to Pursue Data Science Team Management Basics Policy Entrepreneurship at the White House  Productionizing Machine Learning: Pipelines  scikit-learn pandas sklearn-pandas lightgbm Shap: Model Explanations  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/author/jpsl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/author/jpsl/</guid>
      <description>I am the Data Science Team Lead at N26. Over five years in data I’ve optimized digital marketing, applied machine learning to the contemporary art world, built an award winning project in an open data hackathon, and taken on a series of positions at a rather ambitious Berliner fintech.
At the present, I am working on:
 building and mentoring data science teams scaling and managing product-driven ML and data science services developing best practices for data science in a product-driven organization  If we have common interests, please get in touch: hello@jeremiahlewis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>